

■ pedrorcampillo@gmail.com |

pedroruiz.xyz |

pruiz-ca |

pruiz

Career goals

I'm an engineer with experience in data and consumer behaviour. Computers have always been my passion, that's why I decided to join 42 Madrid and become a developer. This has been a process in a disrupting school founded in Paris based on peer to peer learning and self-education, methods with which I identify myself and that I used in other important aspects of my life. My goal now is to advance as a professional in the field being part of a team where I can dedicate and contribute with my high motivation and work ethics.

Experience

42Berlin Berlin, Germany

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | PEDAGO

Jul. 2022 - Current

Staff member of 42 Berlin Software Engineering school which teaches a solid foundation of C/C++. Developed various scripts and backends to
help the school management.

Indra Madrid, Spain

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Jan. 2022 - Jul. 2022

· Working with the Flight Data Processing module and Database Manager of their ATM system. C/C++, Ada & PostgreSQL.

Appen Australia Remote

ADS ASSESSOR

• Ensured ad quality and better user experience with Google and Youtube ads.

ETSIAM - Universidad de Córdoba

Córdoba, Spain

Sep. 2008

Aug. 2012

Jan. 2017 - Dec. 2020

Data Science Intern

Jul. 2015 - Sep. 2016

· Developed Python scripts to automate data analysis and statistics to support MSc Theses @ ETSIAM Economics Department.

Education

42 Madrid Madrid, Spain

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING Dec. 2020 - Jan. 2022

Learned about algorithms, network protocols, memory management & data structures.

Universidad de Córdoba Córdoba, Spain

BSC and MSC in Agricultual Engineering

Focused in Economics, Genetic Engineering & Scientific Research.

Wageningen Universiteit

Wageningen, The Netherlands

MSc in Management, Business and Consumer Behaviour

Learned about marketing, consumer psychology & business management.

Personal Projects

Multiplayer Pong

[ANGULAR, NESTJS, POSTGRESQL, DOCKER] ENTIRE 3D WEBGAME WITH MULTIPLAYER CAPABILITIES AND REALTIME CHAT.

Price predictor

[PYTHON] MACHINE LEARNING USING A GRADIENT DESCENT ALGORITHM TRAINING.

IRC Server

[C++] BASED ON THE RFC PROTOCOL AND SUPPORTS MULTIPLE COMERCIAL CLIENTS.

Containers

[C++] Vector, Stack, Map and Set made from scratch, including a red-black binary tree.

Minishell

[C] PERSONAL SHELL THAT MIMICS BASH BEHAVIOR MADE FROM SCRATCH. 2021

MiniRT

[C] RAYTRACER MADE FROM SCRATCH WITH NO EXTERNAL LIBRARIES. 2021

Skills_

Advanced C, C++, Ada, Python, FastAPI, Flask, Typescript, NestJS, Angular, Docker, Ansible, PostgreSQL, Git, Linux

Languages Spanish & English (fluent)

Other I play guitar in a rock band since 2011. Building electronic devices like tube amps and guitar effects. 3D printing.